Inventory of the Frank and Doris Hursely papers, 1942-1969
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Television Scripts
  - Search For Tomorrow
    - October 24-28, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2381-2385
    - October 31 to November 4, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2386-2390
    - November 7-11, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2391-2395
    - November 14-18, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2396-2400
    - November 21-25, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2401-2405
    - November 28 to December 2, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2406-2410
    - December 5-9, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2411-2415
    - December 12-16, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2416-2420
    - December 19-23, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2421-2425
    - December 26-30, 1960 (Box 121)
      Week #2426-2430
    - January 2-6, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2431-2435
    - January 9-13, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2436-2440
    - January 16-20, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2441-2445
    - January 23-27, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2446-2450
    - January 30 to February 3, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2451-2455
    - February 6-10, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2456-2460
    - February 13-17, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2461-2465
    - February 20-24, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2466-2470
    - February 27 to March 3, 1961 (Box 122)
      Week #2471-2475
    - March 6-10, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2476-2480
    - March 20-24, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2481-2485
    - March 27-31, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2486-2490
    - April 3-7, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2491-2495
    - April 10-14, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2496-2500
    - April 17-21, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2501-2505
    - April 24-28, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2506-2510
    - May 1-5, 1961 (Box 123)
      Week #2511-2515
    - May 8-12, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2521-2525
    - May 15-19, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2526-2530
    - May 22-26, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2531-2535
    - May 29 to June 2, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2536-2540
    - June 5-9, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2541-2545
    - June 12-16, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2546-2550
    - June 19-23, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2551-2555
    - June 26-30, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2556-2560
    - July 3-7, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2561-2565
    - July 10-14, 1961 (Box 124)
      Week #2566-2570
    - July 17-21, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2571-2575
    - July 24-28, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2576-2580
    - July 31 to August 4, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2581-2585
    - August 7-11, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2586-2590
    - August 14-18, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2591-2595
    - August 21-25, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2596-2600
    - August 28 to September 1, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2601-2605
    - September 4-8, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2686-2610
    - September 11-15, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2611-2615
    - September 18-22, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2616-2620
    - September 25-29, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2621-2625
    - October 2-6, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2626-2630
    - October 9-13, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2631-2635
    - October 16-20, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2636-2640
    - October 2 3-27, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2641-2645
    - October 30 to November 3, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2646-2650
    - November 6-10, 1961 (Box 125)
      Week #2651-2655
    - November 13-17, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2656-2660
    - November 20-24, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2661-2665
    - November 27 to December 1, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2666-2670
    - December 4-8, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2671-2675
    - December 11-15, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2676-2680
    - December 18-22, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2681-2685
    - December 25-29, 1961 (Box 127)
      Week #2686-2690
    - January 1-5, 1962 (Box 127)
      Week #2691-2695
    - January 8-12, 1962 (Box 127)
      Week #2696-2700
    - January 15-19, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2701-2705
    - January 23-26, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2706-2710
    - January 29 to February 2, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2711-2715
    - February 5-9, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2716-2120
    - February 12-16, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2721-2725
    - February 19-23, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2726-2730
    - February 26 to March 2, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2731-2735
    - March 5-9, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2736-2740
    - March 12-16, 1962 (Box 128)
      Week #2741-2745
    - March 19-23, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2746-2750
    - March 26-30, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2751-2755
    - April 2-6, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2756-2760
    - April 9-13, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2761-2765
    - April 16-20, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2766-2770
    - April 23-27, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2771-2775
    - April 30 to May 4, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2776-2780
    - May 7-11, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2781-2785
    - May 14-18, 1962 (Box 129)
      Week #2786-2790
    - May 21-25, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2791-2795
    - May 28 to June 1, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2796-2800
    - June 4-8, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2801-2805
    - June 11-15, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2806-2810
    - June 18-22, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2811-2815
    - June 25-29, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2816-2820
    - July 2-6, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2821-2825
    - July 9-13, 1962 (Box 130)
      Week #2826-2830
    - July 16-20, 1969 (Box 131)
      Week #2831-2835
    - July 23-27, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2836-2840
    - July 30 to August 3, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2841-2845
    - August 6-10, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2846-2850
    - August 13-17, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2851-2855
    - August 20-24, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2856-2860
    - August 27-31, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2861-2865
    - September 3-7, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2866-2870
    - September 10-14, 1962 (Box 131)
      Week #2871-2875
    - September 17-21, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2876-2880
    - September 24-28, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2831-2885
    - October 1-5, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2886-2890
    - October 8-12, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2891-2895
    - October 15-19, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2896-2900
    - October 22-26, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2901-2905
    - October 29 to November 2, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2906-2910
    - November 5-9, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2911-2915
    - November 12-16, 1962 (Box 132)
      Week #2916-2920
    - November 19-23, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2921-2925
    - November 26-30, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2926-2930
    - December 3-7, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2931-2935
    - December 10-14, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2936-2940
    - December 17-21, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2941-2945
    - December 24-25, 1962 (Box 133)
      Week #2946-2947
    - January 2-4, 1963 (Box 133)
      Week #2953-2955
    - January 7-10 (Box 133)
      Week #2956-2950
    - January 14-18, 1963 (Box 133)
      Week #2961-2965
    - January 21-25, 1963 (Box 133)
      Week #2966-2970
    - January 28 to February 1, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2971-2975
    - February 4-8, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2976-2980
    - February 11-15, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2981-2935
    - February 18-22, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2986-2990
    - February 25 to March 1, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2991-2995
    - March 4-8, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #2990-3000
    - March 11-15, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #3001-3005
    - March 18-22, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #3006-3010
    - March 25-29, 1963 (Box 134)
      Week #3011-3015
    - April 1-5, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3016-3020
    - April 8-15, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3021-3025
    - April 15-19, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3026-3030
    - April 22-26, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3031-3035
    - April 29 to May 3, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3036-3040
    - May 6-10, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3041-3045
    - May 13-17, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3046-3050
    - May 20-24, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3051-3055
    - May 27-31, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3056-3060
    - June 3-7, 1963 (Box 135)
      Week #3061-3065
    - June 10-14, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3066-3070
    - June 17-21, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3071-3075
    - June 24-28, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3076-3080
    - July 1-5, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3081-3085
    - July 8-12, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3086-3090
    - July 15-19, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3091-3095
    - July 22-26, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3096-3100
    - July 29 to August 2, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3101-3105
    - August 5-9, 1963 (Box 136)
      Week #3106-3110
    - August 12-16, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3111-3115
    - August 19-23, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3116-3120
    - August 26-30, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3121-3125
    - September 2-6, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3131-3135
    - September 9-13, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3136-3140
    - September 16-20, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3141-3145
    - September 23-30, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3146-3150
    - September 31 to October 4, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3151-3155
    - October 7-11, 1963 (Box 137)
      Week #3156-3160
    - October 14-18, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3161-3165
    - October 21-25, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3166-3170
    - October 28 to November 1, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3171-3175
    - November 4-8, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3176-3180
    - November 11-15, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3181-3185
    - November 18-22, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3136-3190
    - November 25-29, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3191-3195
    - December 2-6, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3196-3200
    - December 9-13, 1963 (Box 138)
      Week #3201-3205
    - December 16-20, 1963 (Box 139)
      Week #3206-3210
    - December 23-27, 1963 (Box 139)
      Week #3211-3215
    - December 30-31, 1963 (Box 139)
      Week #3216-3217
    - January 1-3, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3218-3220
    - January 6-10, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3221-3225
    - January 13-17, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3226-3230
    - January 20-24, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3231-3235
    - January 27-31, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3236-3240
    - February 3-7, 1964 (Box 139)
      Week #3241-3245
    - February 10-14, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3246-3250
    - February 17-21, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3251-3255
    - February 24-28, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3256-3260
    - March 2-6, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3261-3265
    - March 9-13, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3266-3270
    - March 16-20, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3271-3275
    - March 23-27, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3276-3280
    - March 30 to April 3, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3281-3285
    - April 6-10, 1964 (Box 140)
      Week #3286-3290
    - April 13-17, 1964 (Box 141)
      Week #3291-3295
    - April 20-24, 1964 (Box 141)
      Week #3296-3300
    - April 27 to May 1, 1964 (Box 141)
      Week #3301-3305
    - May 4-8, 1964 (Box 141)
      Week #3306-3310
    - May 11-15, 1964 (Box 141)
      Week #3311-3315
    - May 18-22, 1964 (Box 142)
      Week #3316-3320
    - May 25-29, 1964 (Box 142)
      Week #3321-3325
    - June 1-5, 1964 (Box 142)
      Week #3326-3330